md shariful islam

summary

software industry. Work as a Full stack Python Developer. Skilled in python , django , Js and its Frameworks. Docker techonology , NoSql, Mongodb

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer

education

Ahsanullah University Of Science and Technology Dhaka, Dhaka Division

Graduated March 2013

employment history

DataShall Analytics Ltd. Full Stack Python Programmer Dhaka, Dhaka Division

1. Telecom Software Architect

August 2017 - Present

2. Database Desing

3. Machine Learning Service Develop

4 Cranhani Cranhal

5.5 million datascrap and cleaning

6. Python automation Script Writting

7. AWS, VPS, Digital Ocean server Ocean

9. Javascript , angular js, redux

10. Nosql, Mongo db, sql, mariadb

11. Work on Linux

Prochito ITS

Software developer

February 2016 - July 2017

1.Software Architect 2.Database Design

3.ERP Development with Django

4.JavaScript, Jquery, Ajax 5. HTTP/REST development experience

6. Experience with relational databases

7. Have good knowledge on GIT

8. Working with ubuntu linux system and Mac 9 Docker

11. Scrapy

hisoft Software developer

March 2015 - January 2016

2. JavaScript, Jquery, Ajax

10. Odoo

3. Wordpress theme Development

4. Plugin Development

wedothewebs Font end developer February 2014 - October 2014

1. Responsive design

2. PSD to html

3. Javascript , Jquery

4. Bootstrap

professional

skills

Django: JavaScript:

Jquery:

SQL, MySQL, sqlite3: Scrappy, datascrap, web scrap:

Docker Technology: Diango Rest Framework: Version Controller GIT management:

HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap4: Linux Ubuntu: NoSQL, MongoDB:

Bangla: ★★★★ English: ★★★★

languages